var myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Why would you surround a piece of text with <h1></h1> tags?",
        answers: {
            a: "to indicate that this text is the main heading on the page",
            b: "to make the text bold",
            c: "to ensure that search engines treat the keywords as being important for this page",
            d: "to demonstrate to screen readers that this text is important"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "When might an empty alt attribute be the correct value?",
        answers: {
            a: "when you cannot think of useful alt text",
            b: "when you don't think it would be interesting to someone who cannot see it",
            c: "when the image has come from a CMS",
            d: "when the image is purely decorative"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which attribute must have a unique value each time it is used in an HTML document",
        answers: {
            a: "title",
            b: "class",
            c: "style",
            d: "id"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which CSS property will not trigger layout recalculation?",
        answers: {
            a: "top",
            b: "opacity",
            c: "width",
            d: "height"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What does the === comparison operator do?",
        answers: {
            a: "It sets one variable equal to another in both value and type",
            b: "It tests for equality of type only",
            c: "It tests for equality of value only",
            d: "It tests for equality of value and type"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which choice is not a value of the type attribute of the <input> element?",
        answers: {
            a: "range",
            b: "address",
            c: "date",
            d: "password"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which choice is not part of CSS box model?",
        answers: {
            a: "margin",
            b: "border",
            c: "paddding",
            d: "paragraph"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which part of the URL https://app.uniswap.org/pool specifies the domain name?",
        answers: {
            a: "https",
            b: "org",
            c: "uniswap.org",
            d: "app.uniswap"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which HTML element is not considered a landmark element?",
        answers: {
            a: "<form>",
            b: "<ul>",
            c: "<main>",
            d: "<nav>"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which statement is true when an HTML tag has been deprecated?",
        answers: {
            a: "It employs code that can be viewed only on a desktop computer",
            b: "It is obsolete and is not recommended for use in marking web content",
            c: "It employs code that will require users to update their browsers",
            d: "It employs incorrect syntax that will cause the browser to crash"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    // {
    //     question: "Which array method should you apply to run a function for every item within an array, returning an array of all items for which the function is true?",
    //     answers: {
    //         a: "every()",
    //         b: "map()",
    //         c: "forEach()",
    //         d: "filter()"
    //     },
    //     correctAnswer: "d"
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "You want to create striped table rows using CSS without adding a class to any element. Which CSS would correctly apply the background color to every odd row in your table?",
    //     answers: {
    //         a: "tr:nth-child(2) { background-color: #ccc; }",
    //         b: "r:nth-child(2n+1) { background-color: #ccc; }",
    //         c: "tr:nth-child(2+1) { background-color: #ccc; }",
    //         d: "tr:nth-child(2n) { background-color: #ccc; }"
    //     },
    //     correctAnswer: "b"
    // }
]